Ding-a-dink-a-l.
They are doing here. I'm gonna be no diggle. I think it's evil left
Diggles diggles mad at me. Everyone's mad at me. Oh nice me more
Guy I move basically can't everyone said no, no, we don't like psyche
it was fun it was fun it was a fun show i knew i couldn't last forever
i'm dark i knew i couldn't last forever i knew i was gonna be here for a short time
the Mary Poppins i'll be like Mary Poppins i'll be there for like a few months maybe like
This year and a half me and this I'll try as long as I can
I haven't been through the world
It was fun
Things have been there it was fun you got Jamie remember it was fun
Was
Jamie you remember forever. It was fun. It was fun
I shot
I'm sorry. If I didn't do a good job, I'm sorry.
As long as you guys are friends, I'm fine.
Remember, you used me as a friend to me tonight. I would be great friends,
Just remember me someday. Just remember me. Just remember me in a good way. Okay?
I never thought anything bad.
I love you, Jamie. Thank you.
Yeah, guys
It's pray so much this about over
Science
It shakes thank you guys be here. Love you guys you so much
You become and say hi
Yeah, was a bite of it. It was here by me
It was fun though, good.
This is my life, this is my life.
That's the time of my life.
I'm going to say a whole thing.
I'm going to say a few things about fish tacos that I like.
I like the way they're sandwiched.
Who heard him?
Did you see him?
What did you say?
Don't want to hear any good bad bad things.
Here.
I got it.
Justin, are you here? Justin Boyle.
Got it. You guys are my friends. No one likes me anymore.
No one likes me anymore. Or just hates me.
Okay, that's impressive.
We're here.
We're here. I'll be right back.
You're here for me. Thank you.
Thank you.
Appreciate it.
Never would you
You ever your friend
I'll have you
Think it has to be weird or weird or anything.
I'll be here for you if you need me, okay?
How is everybody going to answer? Yeah.
Okay, I can never help you. Let me know ever help you anyway
ever
Oh
It's not my name. I'll be there. I love you guys
Does that go in the room?
Sure
You do you guys have a great night, I'm sorry guys. I need to keep you long. I'm sorry guys
Remember
I'll be there
I'll be there. Just stay by me. I'll be there.